

DIVAKAR

FULLSTOCK DEVELOPER

SUMMARY

I am a qualified and professional web developer with two years of experience in database administration and website design. Strong creative and analytical skills. Team player with an eye for detail.

7358832695

- divakarvan03@gmail.com
- Rachandar Thirumalai,621313,Karur
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/divakar-divakar-266178225/

AREAS OF INTEREST

- Full stock Developer
- UI / UX Designer

SKILLS

- Front-End Development:
 HTML,CSS,Bootstrap,Laravel
- Back-End Development : PHP,Javascript
- Databases: Mysql, Mango DB
- Tools: Visual Studio Code, Adobe Creative Suite
- Project Management Tools
- Strong Communication

INTERNSHIPS

- Robotics Pantech ProEd Private
- Artificial Intelligence Pantech Elearning.

ACHIEVEMENTS

- I had worked in more than Fifty live projects.
- I got merit certificate for securing second place in SSLC in my school.
- I had Created transport Booking Website called GoodDe myself.

LANGUAGE

- English Conversational.
- Tamil Native.

EXPERIENCE

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Greymatter Works

2020 - 2021

- Designed and developed high-quality, responsive websites for clients using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and React.
- Built the logic for a streamlined ad-serving platform that scaled
- Educational institutions and online classroom management
- Mentored junior developers and helped to improve their skills and knowledge.

BACK-END DEVELOPER

Greymatter Works

2021 - Present

- Database administration and website design
- Built the logic for a streamlined ad-serving platform that scaled
- Worked with PHP and MySQL to create dynamic, datadriven websites.
- I have six months experience of using laravel Framework

EDUCATION

B.E - CARE College of Engineering, Trichy

2018 -2022

Secured CGPA of 7.7 out of 10

HSC - Government Higher Secondary School, Rachandar Thirumalai 2017-2018

2017 2010

Acquired 77.16% in the board exam

SSLC - Government Higher Secondary School, Rachandar Thirumalai

2015 - 2016

Acquired 90% in the board exam.